Finding Aid for the Ralph Story Papers LSC.0867
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 4. Professional Career/History
  - Publicity and press
    - Western Michigan University News Magazine, vol. 15, no. 2, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      Brief article on page 11 picturing Story and titled, "Ralph Snyder Wins National Fame on TV."
    - Complete TV (August 1957), 1957 August (Box 70, Folder 8)
      Photo essay of Story titled "Bachelor in Hiding" on pages 43 - 45; photographer unidentified.
    - TV Radio Album (March 1957), 1957 March (Box 70, Folder 9)
      Story featured on page 65 within an article titled "The Personality Boys."
    - TV Best (December 1957), 1957 December (Box 70, Folder 10)
      Photo essay of Story titled "Storey [sic]- in Pictures" on pages 30-33; photographer unidentified.
    - TV Star Parade (May 1958), 1958 May (Box 70, Folder 11)
      Photo essay of Story titled "Challenged by Strange Ladies, he Conquered Riches" on pages 18-19, 74; photographer unidentified.
    - Social Service Review, vol. 27, no. 4, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      Article with unidentified author titled "Story's Story" on pages 38-39, 63.
    - TV Guide, vol. 12, no. 28, 1964 July 11 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      Story featured in brief article titled, "Ralph Story's Los Angeles" on pages A4- A5.
    - TV Week: The Daily Report, Ontario/Upland, CA, 5 - 11 June 1966 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      Story featured on cover and advertisement page 21 about the special "The Very Last Resort."
    - TV Week: Citizen News, Hollywood, CA, 1966 June 5-11 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      Story featured on cover and cover close-up article: Dern, Marian. "There's No Story Like Ralph." TV Week: Citizen-News, Hollywood, CA (Jun 5-11, 1966): p.9.
    - TV Week: Independent Star-News, Pasadena, CA, 1966 June 5-11 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      Article from previous file is reproduced on page 9.
    - TV Week: Daily News Tribune, Fullerton, CA, 1967 March 4-10 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      Story featured on cover and cover close-up feature by unidentified author: "Story Tours a Storied Castle." TV Week: Fullerton, CA (4 - 10 March 1967): 21.
    - TV Week: Glendale News-Press, Glendale, CA, 1967 March 4-10 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      Feature from previous file reproduced in same manner on page 21.
    - TV Week: South Bay Daily Breeze, 1967 March 5-11 (Box 70, Folder 19)
      Story featured on cover and in brief paragraph on page 17.
    - The Racquet Club, vol. 8, no. 2, 1969 April (Box 70, Folder 20)
      Story pictured page 2.
    - Parke Bryan's Home Buyers, 1969 May (Box 70, Folder 21)
      Story featured in full page advertisement for KNX News radio.
    - Flight Times, vol. 18, no. 7, 1969 July (Box 70, Folder 22)
      Story featured in short article with unidentified author titled "Story's Voice Set Pattern for Early '6B Flight Service" on page 3.
    - California Men's Stylist, vol. 37, no. 11, 1973 November (Box 70, Folder 23)
      Story interviewed on pages 58-59 by Eirik Knutzen.
    - New York Magazine, vol. 7, no. 51, 1973 December 23 (Box 70, Folder 24)
      Stephanie Edwards featured in article: Hodgetts, Victoria. "Will ABC's Eight- Million-Dollar Baby Pay Off?" New York Magazine, vol. 7, no. 51 (23 December 1973): 38-42.
    - The Bay Window, vol. 28, no.1, 1975 September 19 (Box 70, Folder 25)
      Story profiled in article: Alexander, Toni. "Inside Story." The Bay Window, vol. 28, no. 1 (September 19, 1975): 15-17.
    - Los Angeles Magazine, vol. 22, no. 1, 1977 September (Box 70, Folder 26)
      Story featured in full page advertisement for a product to aid smokers in quitting.
    - Official Olympic Guide to Los Angeles, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 27)
      Story authors article on pages 287-289 titled, "Ralph Story's Parting Shot."
    - Fifth Annual Festival of Preservation Guide, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 28)
      Story pictured on page 27 in conjunction with KNXT TV.
    - Forty-eighth L.A. Area Emmy Awards Guide, 1996 June 1 (Box 70, Folder 29)
      Story nominated on page 8 for the television special, "Things That Aren't Here Anymore."
    - Minute Newsmagazine of Los Angeles Business, 1952 January (Box 71, Folder 1)
      Story featured in a paragraph length article on page 9.
    - Star-News Tournament of Roses edition, 1977 December 28 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Research
    Includes notes, clippings, and copies of magazines likely to have been used as research sources. The majority of the subject matter is related to Los Angeles or Southern California.
    - David Shesgreen file-- terse verse, lyrics and correspondence, 1976 - 1979 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Assorted uncategorized research, 1977 - 2002 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Various topics include: photos of Perricone Quads, Harnett Kane, and autographed photo of Tex Ritter; Beverly Hills; Lawry's; Pasadena; 1972 Academy Awards; Dana Point Ocean Institute; Southern California events and history
    - Herb Caen columns, 1978 August - September (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Show ideas -- train trip, 1986 - 1987 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - AP Laserphotos, 1983 - 1984 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Assorted uncategorized research, 1977 - 1986 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Various topics include: Bridget Boland, Old Wives' Lore for Gardening; Southern California real estate and history; wine; Cretors corn poppers; newswires; mobile broadcasting facilities; San Simeon update
    - Wireless flash rate card and samples, 1984 October - November (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - 4 magazines, 1977 - 1978 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      Peristyle, Winter 1978; Wine World, Jan-Feb 1978; The Mother Earth News, Nov-Dec 1977; Travel and Leisure, October 1978
    - Photos of Mackinac Island and a college-- from Jay Allen on behalf of Reverend Rex Humbard, 1972 February 25 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      5 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Disney research, undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
      11 photographs (8x10 inch black and white), press releases, studio history
    - Assorted uncategorized research -- newspaper sections; Southern California History, 1977 - 1986 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Assorted uncategorized research, 1968 - 1974, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      The California Turtle and Tortoise Club; L.A. Today Custom Tours; a song by Mel Leven; fa?ade easement information; public transportation reports
    - The Jerk -- final draft of script, 1979 February 9 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Audiocassette labeled "Pat Plumleigh, Area Director, The Diet Workshop", undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Jack Benny Program -- script for program #36 rebroadcast, 1957 July 7 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Direct Relief Around the World -- pitches for a documentary produced by Direct Relief International and Quantum Video of Santa Barbara, California, undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Television survey, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Television schedules and program reviews, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Tennis, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Media syllabi of Frank Bock, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Publicity and advertising guide, ca. 1982 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Journalism syllabus, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Radio, late 1990's (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - California and Western U.S. history, ca. 1995 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Small publications -- Official Map Book to the Los Angeles 1984 Olympic Games (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Small publications -- Channel Islands: The Story Behind the Scenes, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Small publications -- AFTRA 60: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists 1937-1997, a Celebration. (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Periodicals -- Pictorial California and the Pacific, 1969 April (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Periodicals -- West: Los Angeles Times Magazine, 1969 November 9 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Periodicals -- West: Los Angeles Times Magazine, 1969 May 25 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Periodicals -- West: Los Angeles Times Magazine, 1970 May 3 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Periodicals -- Environmental Communications, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Periodicals -- Los Angeles Times Home Salute 200!, 1980 August 24 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Periodicals -- Los Angeles 1781-1981, 1980 August 31 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      Advertising supplement to the Los Angeles Times.
    - Periodicals -- Punch, 1982 October 13 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Periodicals -- Punch, 1982 October 20 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- 5. Photographs
  - Press Kit photos -- studio and stage productions, 1973-1975
    - Glynnis Johns, Center Theatre Group at the Ahmanson production of Ring Round the Moon, 1975 April 1 - May 10 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      8 photographs (8x10 inch and cropped, black and white)
    - Glenda Jackson, Huntington Hartford Theatre production of Hedda Gabler, 1975 April 9 - 19 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      7 photographs (8x10 inch and cropped, black and white)
    - Murder on the Orient Express, Paramount Pictures, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      29 photographs (8x10 inch black and white) and 28 caption cards
    - Bug, Paramount Pictures, a William Castle Production, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      5 photographs (8x10 inch black and white) and caption cards
    - Gene Autry, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
      4 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Deborah Kerr, Seascape (a play by Edward Albee), undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
      3 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Tommy, Columbia Pictures, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      15 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - The Prisoner of Second Avenue, Warner Brothers, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      12 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Return of the Pink Panther, United Artists, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      28 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Funny Lady, Columbia Pictures, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      21 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Rafferty and the Gold Dust Twins, Warner Brothers, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Day of the Locust, Paramount Pictures, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      26 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Rollerball, United Artists, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Jaws, Universal Pictures, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      11 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Butely, American Film Theatre, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      8 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - The Yakuza, Warner Brothers, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      7 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Take a Hard Ride, 20th Century Fox, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      13 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Scenes from a Marriage, Ingmar Bergman, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Various press kit photos, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      12 photographs (8x10 inch black and white) including: Beautiful People, Warner Brothers; Cicely Tyson headshot; Lenny, United Artists; Rooster Cogburn, Universal Pictures; Ryan O'Neal; The Godfather Part 2, Paramount Pictures
    - Liberace press portfolio, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Murder on the Orient, Paramount Pictures, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Tommy, Columbia Pictures, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Death on the Nile, Paramount Pictures/EMI, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Historical photographs -- reproductions, undated (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Ralph Story, ca. 1943 - 2003
    Photographs of Ralph Story -- appearances and events, publicity stills.
    - "Thank you for attending my personal appearance" cards with photo of Ralph Story; Assorted unidentified events and publicity still; Revlon, $64,000 Challenge events, 1957 October 24 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      2 postcards; 11 photographs (5x7 inch black and white); 20 photographs (5x7 inch black and white)
    - Receiving key from the Mayor of Orlando; Unidentified event involving "The Drug Center of the Ozark Empire" and KTTS CBS television; Unidentified events and publicity stills, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
      4 photographs (8x10 inch black and white), 1 cropped; 1 photograph (8x10 inch black and white), 3 photographs (5x7 inch black and white); 14 photographs (6x9 and smaller black and white); credits include Globe from Mirror Enterprises Syndicate
    - Assorted photos including: 1 color slide of woman at Hearst Castle; Story and Tichi Wilkerson Miles at Key Art Awards, 1973; various unidentified and undated events and publicity stills (Box 53, Folder 11)
      1 color slide; 21 b & w prints various sizes; credits include: Bruce A. Bromley, Photo World; Lee and Associates, Los Angeles; Carol De Lis; Vanguard Photography, Hollywood; Joe Flowers, Los Angeles; Keller Photo, Beverly Hills
    - Assorted photos, unidentified, various, including early 1980s (Box 53, Folder 12)
      2 photographs (5x7 inch color and black and white) with Lorne Green and others at Tournament of Roses event; 2 color photographs, 5x7 inch, from the Wine Game; 1 color photographs, 8x10 inch, with CBS TV news team, including Connie Chung and Marcia Brandywynne; 1 color photograph, 8x10 inch, with CBS crew; 1 black and white photograph, 8x10 inch, Story with ABC 7 camera; 1 black and white photograph, 8x10 inch, unidentified man and woman; 1 black and white photograph, 8x10 inch, Story with Universal Studios Senior Star Micaela Mesa; 3 black and white photographs, 8x10 inch, action shots playing tennis in old fashioned attire; 6 black and white photographs, 8x10 inch, Story at unidentified events. Credits include: Joe Bardo, Glendale, California; Judy Houston; Phil Glickman, Sherman Oaks, California
    - Old CBS photos -- contact prints of headshots and circus-theme publicity stills, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
      16 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Head shots, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
      8 photographs (8x10 inch black and white, some duplicates), 3 with CBS Photo credit by Gabor Rona
    - $64,000 question/Revlon personal appearances, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
      7 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)-- credits include Wilson C. Burton of Hammel's Studio, Mobile, Alabama; Al Williams of Central Studio, Kalamazoo, Michigan; Lubitsch and Bungarz, Wilmington, Delaware
    - 23rd annual meeting of the National Association of Food Chains, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
      7 photographs (8x10 inch black and white), Story posing with meeting attendees
    - Spirit of Achievement Awards presented to Agnes DeMille, Sophie Gimbel, Mrs. David M. Levy, and Jean Kerr by the Women's Division, Albert Einstein College of Medicine of Yeshiva University, 1958 March 24 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Costume event Marina Del Rey, NBC camera in one shot, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Agatha Christie s?ance -- KNXT/CBS News segment, 1979 February 8 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Live appearance, unidentified mall, many women and babies, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
      10 photographs (8x10 inch black and white)
    - Visit to Lily-Tulip plant, Springfield, Missouri, 1956 November 20 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Assorted unidentified publicity stills and event photos with CBS Photo credits, various undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
      27 photographs (8x10 inch black and white), photographers include J. Winston Pennock, Pierce Grant, Walt Davis, Ed Braslaff, Gabor Rona, Ted Holmes, Art Lewis
    - Assorted unidentified event photos, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
      26 photographs (8x10 inch black and white), credits include William Eccles, Los Angeles Airport Photography; Martin's Studio, Greensboro, North Carolina; Maas Brothers, Tampa, Florida; Sid Avery and associates, Hollywood, California and So. Calif. Broadcasters Assn. Inc.; Chuck Ross Studio, Hollywood, California; Terry Junkins, Los Angeles, California; American Stock photos, Los Angeles, California; Irv Antler, Ambassador Hotel, Los Angeles, California; Larry Woerner; Dave Alvaranza, Pasadena City College; Ed Braslaff, Hollywood, California
    - Assorted unidentified publicity stills, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
      7 photographs (8x10 inch black and white), credits include: Albert Gommi, New York, New York; Globe photos, New York
    - Party at the home of Mr. and Mrs. William Kretzer, 1957 January 9; Ralph Story with Eloise English, Don Ross and others, undated; Ralph Story with Tom Irish of the Wally Findlay Galleries and Bob Wright, Australian Assistant Trade Commissioner, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      4 photographs (8x10 inch black and white), letter
    - Board mounted oversized b&w photos Story at work, KNXT CBS (Box 59, Folder 1)
      8 photos cropped to varying sizes
    - Oversized photos Story at work, one with Stephanie Edwards (Box 59, Folder 2)
      5 photographs (11x14 inch black and white)
    - Oversized publicity shots for "It's a nice place?", 1967 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      8 photographs (9.5x14 inch black and white)
    - Air Force portraits, ca. 1943 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Travel snapshots and foreign currency, ca. 1953 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Headshots, ca. 1954 - 1996 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - CBS photographs, ca. 1955 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Events and Appearances, ca. 1955 - 1993 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Broadcasting, ca. 1955 - 1995 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Globe photo shoot, ca. 1957 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Broadcasting -- contact sheets, ca. 1957 - 1965 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Theater, ca. 1959 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS -- "The Very Last Resort", ca. 1966 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Tennis, ca. 1970 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified photo shoot slides, ca. 1971 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Signed photographs given to Story, ca. 1973 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified event, ca. 1975 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Silverado Day Parade slides, 1977 November 14 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Porciuncula research photographs, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Story at Grauman's Theater in Hollywood -- negatives, undated (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Oversize photographs, ca. 1948 - 1980 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- 6. Personal life
  Includes memorablia collected by Story including personal correspondence, photo and clipping albums, vinyl records, and sheet music.
  - Childhood project -- "My Health Book", 1929 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Piano recital programs, ca. 1930 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with Marjorie Snyder (Story's mother), 1932 - 1951 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - "The Delphian" -- Kalamazoo Central High School, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Preflight magazine, 1943 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    Includes correspondence to Story's mother on the back cover.
  - WGR album, ca. 1948 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Early CBS radio album, ca. 1950 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Clippings album, ca. 1954 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Also includes a small number of items and photographs from Story's childhood indicating the album may have been kept by Story's mother.
  - Script -- Bernard Shaw's play, "Don Juan in Hell", 1960 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    This is Story's personal script for his role as the Devil in this play.
  - Playbills, ca. 1960 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Rev. Parker Moloney, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Cat clippings, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    Includes hand-colored piece of cloth.
  - Fighter award album, undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - "Freedom of the Press" booklet, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Sheet music by Albert Hay Malotte, undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
    Includes 7" record, "Lullaby" narrated by Story.
  - Vinyl Records Album, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Vinyl Records, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
    Includes one record which Story narrated called, "Lullaby."
  - Revlon/Crank's album -- "Ralph Story visits Springfield, MO", ca. 1956 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - CBS departure album, ca. 1955 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Album presented to Story by colleagues at KNXT/CBS radio preceding his departure to host the "$64,000 Challenge."
  - "Things that aren't here anymore" poster (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - "$64,000 Challenge" album, ca. 1956-1958 (Box 75, Folder 3)